<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Decode &amp; Deploy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Decode &amp; Deploy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RNA seq pipeline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/pipelines/2024-05-02-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/pipelines/2024-05-02-/</guid>
      <description> Highlevel Create Singularity Container with following packages:&#xA;fastp HISAT2 StringTie Use this container in HPC to Convert FASTQ files to Gene counts&#xA;Create a Docker Bioconductor container with following packages:&#xA;Deseq2 clusterProfiler Use the Bioconductor Docker container to perform for following:&#xA;Exploratory Data analysis Differential Gene Expression ORA GSEA Generate Plots as needed Make Dashboards </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene Count Boxplots</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/2024-04-30-gc-plots-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/2024-04-30-gc-plots-v2/</guid>
      <description>Preface When Differential gene expression between two groups is computed it may be good idea to visualize the top DEG gene count distribution between the groups.&#xA;This document shows how to generate Boxplots for the top DEG using the Variance stabilized counts from RNA seq results.&#xA;Required files for Gene counts Boxplots:&#xA;Metadata/phenotype file &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; metadata&#xA;VST Normalized counts &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; vst_counts&#xA;DEG results &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; deg_res (The top few differentially expressed genes)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder.&#xA;Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typography Styles &amp; Element Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/elements/</guid>
      <description>Font Sizes A A A A A A A A 6rem&#xA;(96px) 5rem&#xA;(80px) 3rem&#xA;(48px) 2.25rem&#xA;(36px) 1.5rem&#xA;(24px) 1.25rem&#xA;(20px) 1rem&#xA;(16px) .875rem&#xA;(14px) Type Samples Head&amp;shy;line Sub&amp;shy;head&amp;shy;line Level 1 Heading One page to rule them all...well, not really. This page displays sample typography and page elements to illustrate their style. Things like headings and paragraphs showing the beautiful type scale, form elements, tabular data, and image layouts just to name a few.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:&#xA;Desirée De Leon &amp;#x1f992; (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)&#xA;Garrick Aden-Buie &amp;#x1f9d9; (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)&#xA;Allison Horst &amp;#x1f415; (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot &amp;#x1f994;)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/license/</guid>
      <description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
